<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<root>
    <debug>
        <value>2</value>
        <name>debug</name>
        <default>2</default>
        <help>CakePHP Debug Level:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             Production Mode:&lt;br&gt;             0: No error messages, errors, or warnings shown. Flash messages redirect.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             Development Mode:&lt;br&gt;             1: Errors and warnings shown, model caches refreshed, flash messages halted.&lt;br&gt;             2: As in 1, but also with full debug messages and SQL output.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;             In production mode, flash messages redirect after a time interval.&lt;br&gt;             In development mode, you need to click the flash message to continue.&lt;br&gt;</help>
    </debug>
    <Security.level>
        <value>'medium'</value>
        <name>Security.level</name>
        <default>'medium'</default>
        <help>The level of CakePHP security.</help>
    </Security.level>
    <Session>
        <value>array('defaults' =&gt; 'php')</value>
        <name>Session</name>
        <default>array('defaults' =&gt; 'php')</default>
        <help>Session configuration.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         Contains an array of settings to use for session configuration. The defaults key is&lt;br&gt;         used to define a default preset to use for sessions, any settings declared here will override&lt;br&gt;         the settings of the default config.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         ## Options&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         - `Session.cookie` - The name of the cookie to use. Defaults to 'CAKEPHP'&lt;br&gt;         - `Session.timeout` - The number of minutes you want sessions to live for. This timeout is handled by CakePHP&lt;br&gt;         - `Session.cookieTimeout` - The number of minutes you want session cookies to live for.&lt;br&gt;         - `Session.checkAgent` - Do you want the user agent to be checked when starting sessions? You might want to set the&lt;br&gt;            value to false, when dealing with older versions of IE, Chrome Frame or certain web-browsing devices and AJAX         - `Session.defaults` - The default configuration set to use as a basis for your session.&lt;br&gt;            There are four builtins: php, cake, cache, database.         - `Session.handler` - Can be used to enable a custom session handler.  Expects an array of of callables,&lt;br&gt;            that can be used with `session_save_handler`.  Using this option will automatically add `session.save_handler`            to the ini array.         - `Session.autoRegenerate` - Enabling this setting, turns on automatic renewal of sessions, and&lt;br&gt;            sessionids that change frequently. See CakeSession::$requestCountdown.         - `Session.ini` - An associative array of additional ini values to set.&lt;br&gt;         The built in defaults are:&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         - 'php' - Uses settings defined in your php.ini.&lt;br&gt;         - 'cake' - Saves session files in CakePHP's /tmp directory.&lt;br&gt;         - 'database' - Uses CakePHP's database sessions.&lt;br&gt;         - 'cache' - Use the Cache class to save sessions.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         To define a custom session handler, save it at /app/Model/Datasource/Session/&lt;name&gt;.php.&lt;br&gt;         Make sure the class implements `CakeSessionHandlerInterface` and set Session.handler to &lt;name&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;         To use database sessions, run the app/Config/Schema/sessions.php schema using&lt;br&gt;         the cake shell command: cake schema create Sessions&lt;br&gt;</help>
    </Session>
</root>